teachers.tv 2009-06-20

# Privacy Policy | Teachers TV

## General Information

The Teachers TV channel and the website [www.teachers.tv](http://www.teachers.tv/ "www.teachers.tv") are managed by Education Digital Management Limited. Education Digital Management Limited is responsible for the content of the teachers.tv website and this Privacy Statement applies to that website only. 

## Teachers TV Privacy Statement

Teachers TV and its service providers will use any personal information collected from this website ([www.teachers.tv](http://www.teachers.tv/ "www.teachers.tv")) in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 ('the Act'). Further information about the Act can be found at the website of the Information Commissioner. Teachers TV has taken appropriate measures to keep secure all personal information given by users of this site. This personal information will only ever be used for communicating with you about Teachers TV and we will not sell your information to any third parties.

When you visit the website, a small text file known as a cookie will be downloaded to your computer. This is a common practice which allows Teachers TV to provide you with a better website by keeping track of the areas of the website you visit, for example your areas of specific interest. A cookie may allow Teachers TV to recognise repeat visits and recall information which you have previously supplied to Teachers TV, such as your name. You may adjust how your computer deals with cookies using your internet browser.

## What information do we collect and why?

The information collected on this site includes email addresses and/or other contact details and information which users voluntarily provide in order to register to receive information from Teachers TV and/or our partners and for us to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you. Teachers TV will not disclose voluntarily-provided details to third parties or use the information in any other way without prior consent.   

## Your rights

You have the right to access your information held by Teachers TV and where necessary, to have it amended. For more details, please contact: Data Protection, Rights Department, Teachers TV, 16-18 Berners Street, London W1T 3LN or email [info@teachers.tv](mailto:info@teachers.tv). You can also request not to receive marketing information from Teachers TV by sending a blank email to [unsubscribe@teachers.tv](mailto:unsubscribe@teachers.tv)

## Links to other websites

This website contains links to other sites that are completely unrelated to Teachers TV. This privacy statement does not apply to these other sites nor are we responsible for the content and practices of these websites.

## Data Controller

The Data Controller for the purposes of the Act is the Department for Education and Skills of Sanctuary Buildings, Great Smith Street, Westminster, London SW1P 3BT.
